SSK字幕組
所以我們真的要住這裏嗎
So we're really gonna stay.
你知道在巴黎我都經歷了什麼
Well, you know what Paris does to me.
迪奧 拉格斐爾
Dior, Lagerfeld.
你真該看看他們的工作室
You should see their ateliers.
我希望我也能在那樣的地方工作
I want mine to be right here.
這裏能夠激發我的靈感
This place inspires me.
你可以接受嗎
Is that okay with you?
可以
Yeah.
我交了幾個朋友
I made some friends.
如果我告訴你
What would you think if I told you
我和我那位金髮的女性朋友在一起了
that me and my blonde lady friend are gonna
你是怎麼想的
be together forever?
我以為你喜歡男人
I thought you liked men?
這個嘛 大人的事情總是很複雜的
Well, adults are complicated.
那我接受
Then I approve.
德雷克先生
Mr. Drake.
我覺得我們遇到問題了
I think we've got a problem.
一英吋厚的鋼板
It's one-inch steel.
這裏全部被擋住了
It runs the whole length of this section.
計劃里可沒有這個
It's not in any of the plans.
把它挖出來
Tear it out.
就按預定計劃行事
I'm on a schedule.
這裏聞起來像一坨屎
It smells like shit in there.
不 聞起來像死了人
No, it smells like death.
我覺得我們不應該下到那裏去
I don't think we should go down there.
噢 聞起來像死了人耶
"Eh, it smells like death."
別慫了 你個軟蛋
Come on, you pussy.
這個地方都與世隔絕這麼多年了
This place has been sealed up for years.
SSK字幕組譯制
翻譯  lala小公舉
翻譯  花卷兒
翻譯  Espionage
翻譯  Alex 惡熏
校對  lala小公舉 Bunny
時間軸  Hima
壓制
hhjie
壓制  hhjie
總監  Bunny
推薦關注
Luv_DC
美國恐怖故事
旅館
字幕由SSK字幕組傾情譯制
僅供學習，勿用於商，轉載請註明出處，版權歸片方所有
你知道你是誰嗎
Do you know who you are?
官網：www.sskzmz.com
更多內容可以關注我們的新浪微博
加利福尼亞
California.
哪個醫院
Which hospital?
洛先生 你現在在西加利福尼亞健康中心
Mr. Lowe, you're at the West Los Angeles Health Center.
我想問你幾個問題
I'd like to ask you some questions
來評估你的心理狀態
to determine your state of mind.
你能從一百開始七個數字一隔地往回數嗎
Could you start by counting backwards from 100 by sevens?
呃 九十三
Uh, 93...
八十六
86...
七 七十九
seventy... seventy-nine....
額 我說到哪了
Uh, what was the last one I said?
告訴我以下哪個句子最能準確描述
Tell me which statement most accurately describes
你現在的感覺
what you're feeling.
我沒有對未來失去信心
"I am not discouraged about my future."
你確定你想待在這裏嗎
Are you sure you want to stay here?
我是說 別的地方更舒服一些 約翰
I mean, there are more comfortable places, John.
我可以把你帶回雷斯尼克
I could get you into Resnick.
我覺得這裏很好
This is perfect for me.
你可以用自己的話表述來這裏的原因嗎
In your own words, can you tell me why you're here?
我 呃 我覺得這一切快把我逼到絕境了
I, um, feel like everything's closing in on me.
工作上的不順心
Some setbacks at work.
和妻子長期分居
Separation from my wife.
因為一個誤會
Because of a misunderstanding,
我的女兒害怕我
my daughter is afraid of me.
我需要專業的幫助
I need professional help.
我認為這是一個非常重要的表述
I think that's a very important statement.
事實上你意識到了自己的脆弱
The fact that you recognized your own fragility
並且採取了積極的行動
and took positive action.
有沒有哪一件事
Was there a specific incident
直接促成了最後的結果
that prompted this latest episode?
我一直在解決一個很讓人沮喪的案子
I've been working on a very frustrating case.
有一個殺人犯正在逍遙法外
There's a killer out there, murdering with impunity,
打著十誡的旗號大肆殺人
using the Ten Commandments as justification.
喂 蠢貨 你現在正在行政休假
Hey, dickhead, you're on administrative leave.
如果局長看到你在這 那你原來的工作也別想保住了
Captain sees you here, you won't even get your old job back.
嫌疑人是誰
Who's the suspect?
我不會再幫你打掩護了
I'm not covering for you anymore.
我想跟他談談
I want to talk to him.
他在哪
Where is he?
我攻擊了我唯一的朋友
I attacked the only friend I had.
唯一一個試圖幫我的人
The one person who was trying to help me.
那就是你最終意識到你需要幫助的原因嗎
And that's when you finally realized you needed help.
呼吸些新鮮空氣吧
Get some fresh air.
你最好滾得遠遠的 混蛋
You better be out of here, asshole!
好 我這就走
Okay, I'm going.
我知道我確實應該去醫院看看了
I knew it was time I checked into a hospital.
我們會處理好的 約翰
We'll get a handle on this, John.
這是一個良好的開端
This is a good first step.
我覺得這裏就是我應該在的地方
I feel I'm exactly where I need to be.
德雷克先生知道這個嗎
Does Mr. Drake know about this?
呃 我不覺得
Um, I don't think so.
他 呃 他正在忙著
He's, um, he's in the middle
給自己的菊花上潤滑劑和漂白吧
of getting his anus waxed and bleached.
現在流行起這個了嗎
Is that a thing now?
我的意思是 怎麼會有人覺得
I mean, how would someone even know
自己的菊花應該漂個白
their anus needs bleaching?
不是天下菊花一般黑嗎
I couldn't pick my butthole out of a lineup.
這是誰幹的
Who did this?
不是新來的保姆吧
Not the new governess.
不是
No.
我是說 你看看他們的慘狀
I mean, look at 'em.
這得是多飢渴才會做出這種事
Whoever did this was starving.
裏面有什麼
What was in here?
我不知道
I don't know.
怎麼了
What?
我只是之前從沒見過你害怕
I've just never seen you scared before.
我讓他相信他這一票賺大了
I convinced him I got him a fantastic deal,
所以他除了佣金之外還給我放了一個週末的假
so he threw a free weekend on top of my commission.
別告訴他那些文件是我編的
Don't tell him that I fudged the paperwork
好讓他覺得有不少人競標來著
to make it look like he had multiple offers.
喔寶貝
Oh, honey.
我更想一個人呆著
I'd rather be alone.
你知道嗎 自從我不得不把哈莉放倒
You know, ever since I had to put Hallie down,
我常常因為痛苦而抽搐
I go through these spasms of grief.
喔 房間服務來了
Oh, there's the room service.
拜拜 瑪格麗特
Bye, Margaret.
這個婊子真討厭
I hate that bitch.
馬上來 我的天哪
All right! I'm coming. For God's sake...
啊
Aah!
以眼還眼
An eye for an eye.
以牙還牙
A tooth for a tooth!
這是我父親的鐵律
That is the law of my father!
你是酋長的女人
You belong to the sheik!
卡 好的我們再拍一條
And cut. Good, let's do one more.
我的天啊 他
My God, he is
美極了
so beautiful.
我男朋友說他是個同性戀
My boyfriend says he's queer.
吉比 他娶了
Gibby. He's married
娜塔莎·蘭波娃
to Natacha Rambova,
世界上最有異域風情的女人
one of the most exotic women in the whole world.
他們現在在鬧離婚 你沒看《每日畫報》嗎
They're getting a divorce. Don't you read Picture Play?
而且她的名字不是蘭波娃
And her name's not Rambova.
是威妮弗雷德·赫德納特
It's Winifred Hudnut.
她來自猶他州
And she's from Utah.
那又怎樣 這只會讓我
So what? That just
更加欣賞她
makes me admire her more.
她簡直是脫胎換骨
She transformed herself.
她唯一改變了的只是他的事業吧
The only thing she transformed is his career.
她把它全毀了
She ruined it.
好萊塢
好了各位 奴隸和宮女嬪妃
Okay, people. Slavers and harem concubines--
準備上場
you're up.
這是給你的 他寫的
This is for you. From him.
與我共度今晚吧
奧拉花園    72號房
瓦倫蒂諾
小美人
Bellissima. Mm.
你來了
You came.
請吧
Please.
我真高興你願意來找我
I am so pleased you agreed to join me.
你知道的 我
You see, I...
我總是只能一個人吃晚飯
I often must dine alone.
-你嗎 -恩
- You? - Mm.
真難以置信
That's hard to believe.
這對我來說實在是煎熬 你知道嗎
Well, it's not simple for me, you know?
名和利
Fame is its own kind
只是另一種枷鎖罷了
of, uh, prison.
請坐
Please.
只是這張臉龐我無法逃避
這面龐真是驚為天人
It's a wonderful face.
你竟然會說意大利語
You speak Italian!
能聽得懂
Well, I understand it, anyway.
我來自本森赫斯特
I'm from Bensonhurst.
我小時候周圍的人都只說意大利語
Italian's all my folks talked
我爸爸來自西西里島
when I was growing up. Pop's from Sicily.
-他是個水管工 -恩
- He's a plumber. - Mm.
所以你懷揣著成為女演員的夢想
And you have come to Hollywood
來到了好萊塢
with dreams of becoming an actress.
這真不幸
That is unfortunate.
我覺得你可以比這個更加偉大
I think I see greater things in you.
比不朽還要偉大
Greater than being immortal?
因為我覺得在大銀幕上表演就意味著不朽
'Cause that's what it means to be up on that screen.
只是個影子
Shadows only.
頂多一個世紀
A hundred years and no one
人們就不會記得我們做過什麼了
will remember what we did.
我不同意
No, I don't agree.
我完全不同意
I don't agree at all.
我覺得電影就是未來
I think the flickers are the future.
這是一種真正的美國藝術
A true American art form.
你才是真正的美國藝術
You are a true American art form.
你是在取笑我嗎
Are you making fun of me?
不不不 小姑娘
No, no, no, little one.
我是在 讚美你
I am, uh... admiring you.
真抱歉 如果你誤解了我的意思
I'm sorry. If it seems otherwise,
那全都是因為
it is only because...
我的英語不好
my English is not so good, huh?
在無需語言的方面
I do better
我可以做的更好
without words.
恩
Mm.
所以
So...
這就是那隻小老鼠
this is the mouse.
喔天哪 你是
Oh, my God, you're...
我是貓
The cat...
小老鼠
little mouse.
這是我妻子 娜塔莎
This is my wife, Natacha.
蘭波娃
Rambova.
我真的 真的很抱歉 我以為
I am... so sorry, I thought...
我在和丈夫鬧離婚嗎
That I was divorcing my husband.
沒錯呀
And so I am.
我 我該走了
I sh...should go.
不不不 別這麼著急呀
No, no, no. Please, not yet, huh?
別走
Stay.
娜塔莎
Natacha...
你對我們的客人溫柔一點 好嗎
you must be gentle with our guest, huh?
離婚只是一場戲
The divorce is for show.
多年以來
The studio has been trying to...
片方都想要把我們倆拆散
tear us apart for years.
所以我們決定
We have decided the only way
唯一能夠在一起的辦法就是
we can really be together is if...
讓全世界都以為我們不在一起了
the world thinks we are not.
我不明白
I don't understand.
為什麼要我來這
Why am I here?
因為 小老鼠
Because, little mouse...
人總有七情六慾嘛
...gods have appetites.
我聽說他不光有錢 而且還單身
I hear he's not only rich, but single
還超帥 可真棒呀
and handsome, so far as that goes.
-你怎麼認識他的 -我還沒跟他見過面呢
- How'd you meet this guy, anyway? - I haven't met him yet.
城裏沒有哪個摩登女郎
There isn't a flapper in this city who hasn't been invited
沒被他邀請去私人派對的
to one of his private wingdings. You'd know that
要不是你整個夏天都沒在圈裏混 你早就知道了
if you hadn't been out of circulation all summer.
我一直都在
I've been around.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
好吧 我忍不住了
Okay, I can't take it anymore.
我真的很想問 你一直跑去見誰啊
So spill-- who have you been seeing?
沒誰
Nobody.
撒謊 你可騙不了我
Lies. You can't fool me.
你戀愛了 不是嗎
You're in love, aren't you?
我很高興歡迎諸位來到科爾特茲旅館的
I'd like to welcome you all to the opening week
開業周活動
of the Hotel Cortez!
很遺憾我們不能
A shame we can't all
在我的新藍鸚鵡廳裏
enjoy these libations
享受開酒儀式
in my new Blue Parrot Lounge, but...
除非有誰良心發現把那該死的
until someone with some sense repeals that nasty
禁酒法案給廢掉
Volstead Act,
不然我和卡朋先生
both I and Mr. Capone
就只能將就了
will have to make due.
阿
Ah!
他死了
He's dead!
瓦倫蒂諾死了
Valentino's dead.
他今天早晨在紐約去世了
He died in New York this morning.
他的電影剛剛上映
And his movie just came out.
我賭票房肯定大賣
Bet the box office goes through the roof.
你的心臟跳的像蜂鳥一樣快
Your heart's beating like a hummingbird.
放開我
Let me go!
不 我不會放開你的
No. I don't suppose I will.
噓
Shh...
實際上
In fact...
我可能永遠也不會放你走
I may never let you go.
真是太悲慘了
It's just so... tragic.
我們好像錯過她了
I guess we missed her.
誰
Who?
黑衣女郎
The Lady in Black.
幾個月來她每天都會來
She's been coming here for months every day
留下一支紅色玫瑰
and leaving a single red rose.
我以為那只是傳聞而已
I thought that was a myth.
不 是真的
No, it's true.
這裏寫的很清楚
It says so right here.
「有謠言稱神秘人
"Rumors have sprung up of a mysterious figure
到訪瓦倫蒂諾之墓」
"Visiting Valentino's tomb.
「有位黑衣女郎 在瓦倫蒂諾八月離世後
"The Lady In Black has left a single red rose
每天在這位偉大的情聖的墓旁
"Next to the Great Lover's final resting place
放一支紅色玫瑰
"Each day since his death last August.
有人說這位帶面紗的女士是女演員寶拉·內歌裏
"Some say the veiled figure is movie actress Pola Negri,
眾所周知 她曾在瓦倫提諾的婚禮上歇斯底里地爆發」
who famously collapsed at Valentino's funeral."
婊子 她可沒愛過他
Harlot. She never loved him.
「還有人相信這位沉默探望者
"Others believed the wordless visitor is something else...
並非地球生物」
something not of this Earth."
好吧 為了賣雜誌他們什麼都能掰
Well, they'll print anything to sell magazines.
呃 女士們
Uh... ladies?
也許我們該迴避一下
Maybe we should give her her privacy.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
你為何流淚
Why do you weep so,
小老鼠
little mouse?
娜塔莎 這段時間你都在哪
Natacha. Where have you been?
到處走走
Here and there.
我給你寫信了 好多封 你從沒有回信
I wrote to you, so many times-- I never heard back.
你連他的葬禮都沒有來
You didn't even come to his funeral.
我為何要去一個活人的葬禮
Why would I go to the funeral of a man who isn't dead?
小美人
Bellisima.
不可能
It can't be true.
你死了
You died.
然後我
And am...
重生了
reborn.
那墓裏的不是魯迪
The body in that crypt isn't Rudy.
是我了不起的替身 喬治·菲斯克
It's my stunt double, George Fiske.
-永遠這麼忠誠 -即使是死這件事
- Always so loyal. - Even in death.
但是要說明的是 我的表演大多是真刀真槍的
Though to be clear, I did do most of my own stunts.
只不過這次不是
Just not this one.
你偽造了你的死亡
You faked your death?!
我愛你們兩個
I loved you both.
而你們就讓我以為你真的死了
And you just let me think the worst?
我差點悲傷而死
I almost didn't survive it.
但你沒有
But you did survive.
而且你很快走出來了
And in some style.
順祝你新婚愉快
Congratulations on the nuptials, by the way.
這麼快就找到了下一任
That was quick.
你想怎樣
What did you expect?
在這個世界上我孤身一人
I was all alone in the world.
我決定
I decided that
如果我注定要悲傷度過餘生
if I was to live in grief,
我也想
I might as well...
被美麗的東西
be surrounded by...
環繞
beautiful things.
即使要跟一個
Even if it was with a man
我根本沒感覺的男人在一起
for whom I felt... nothing.
我被拖入他內心深處的無邊黑暗中
I was drawn to the darkness I felt within him,
被婚姻
I ached...
消耗
to be...
我是如此痛苦
consumed by it.
親愛的
Darling...
你真是激發我所有的潛能啊
you are a revelation.
他使我發現了
He uncovered in me
自己身上前所未見的東西
things I never thought possible.
呃
Uh...
他是誰
Who is he?
就是個流浪漢
Just a hobo.
你不同意
You disapprove?
我不
I do.
你為何要浪費時間殺幾個窮要飯的
Why waste your time killing some destitute beggar?
這樣有什麼好處
What's to be gained?
選一個有錢或者珠寶的獵物
Select a victim with money or jewels.
這樣你的小愛好就能使我們倆都獲益
Then your little hobby can benefit us both.
下一次
And next time...
我想看著你做
...I want to watch.
你經歷了太多痛苦
You have suffered too much.
我不覺得痛苦
I don't suffer.
-不再覺得痛苦了 -你的眼淚告訴我你在說謊
- Not anymore. - Your tears tell me otherwise.
我沒有任何感覺
I feel nothing.
我們不是想要拋棄你 小姑娘
We never meant to leave you this way, little one.
那你們為什麼要那麼做
Then why did you?
造化弄人
Fate intervened.
我在全國到處跑
I was travelling the country,
宣傳《酋長之子》
promoting Son of the Sheik.
在新世紀公司的列車上旅行
Booked on the 20th Century Limited,
從舊金山一直到紐約
the tour would take me from San Francisco to New York,
每一站都被媒體圍追堵截
with press stops all along the way.
我開始留意一個每一站都出現的男人 最開始
At each stop, I began to notice a man. At first,
我以為他也是報社的
I thought he was a member of the press,
但他從不問任何問題
but he never asked any questions,
也不寫任何筆記 他只是注視著我
never wrote anything down. He just watched me,
他的眼神從不離開我
his eyes never leaving me.
這當然很不尋常
This was not unusual, of course.
但那雙眼睛
But something in those eyes...
讓人著迷
mesmerizing.
在火車上 我總是覺得
Again on the train, I began to feel a presence
有什麼東西讓我毛骨悚然
which raised the hairs on the back of my neck.
我感覺在整列火車上
I imagined I was seeing him
到處都是他的影子
all throughout the train.
我開始懷疑我是不是出問題了
I began to doubt my senses.
恐懼像裹屍布一樣圍繞著我
A feeling of dread hung over me like a shroud.
而有一天
And somewhere,
在中西部無盡的平原上行駛的時候
along an endless expanse of Midwest plains,
我從無夢的睡眠中醒來 卻彷彿踏入了夢境中
I woke from a dreamless sleep into a dream itself.
那是一種誘惑 但是肉慾卻不是他的目的
It was a seduction, but mere carnality was not his aim.
電光火石間我便無法自拔
I was repelled and drawn in all at once.
當他開口時 他說的是摻雜著濃濃德國口音
When he spoke, it was in Italian
的意大利語
but with a thick German accent.
他告訴我他的名字是F·W·穆爾諾
He revealed to me his name, F.W. Murnau,
一位德國大導演
the great German director.
他想要你幹什麼呢
What did he want from you?
我以為他想殺了我
I thought he meant to kill me.
但他其實是想讓我「留存」下來
But instead he wished to preserve me.
我不明白
I don't understand.
一開始我也不明白
Neither did I, at first.
在完成他的傑作《不死殭屍》的過程中
The great director had uncovered many secrets
這位偉大的導演發現了許多秘密
in the making of his masterpiece, Nosferatu.
為了完成他的影片 他深入到
To make his picture, he travelled deep
喀爾巴阡山脈之中
into the Carpathian Mountains.
他追求真實性
He demanded authenticity,
那也正是他在那片古老的世界中找到的東西
and that is what he found in that Old World.
他在銀幕上所描繪的那種生物
Creatures like the one he was depicting onscreen,
不像他的男主角馬科斯·夏瑞克那樣可怕
though not hideous like his star, Max Schreck,
反而是無與倫比的美麗
but beautiful beyond compare.
被一種古老的血液病毒所感染
Infected with an ancient blood virus,
其結果就是永生
the consequence of which was eternal life,
永葆青春
endless youth.
但也會產生一種可怕的飢渴
But also a terrible thirst.
他說告訴我所有這一切 是一種預告
He was telling me all this, he said, as a prelude,
既是警告的預告 也是禮物的饋贈
a prelude to a warning and the offer of a gift.
茂瑙對我哀嘆
Murnau lamented to me what he foresees,
他預剪到有聲電影的到來
the coming of talking pictures.
而這意味著諸神的死亡
And with that, the death of the gods.
在最多一年之內 我們的世界將會消亡
Within a year, no more, our world would be gone.
他說 他不能拯救這個世界 但他能拯救我
He couldn't save the world, he said, but he could save me,
讓我永葆美麗
preserve my beauty for all eternity,
但是我得離開銀幕才行
but only if I was ready to leave the screen.
永遠離開
Forever.
所以 一個冰冷的碰觸
And so, with a cool touch,
和一個溫暖的親吻之後 我真正的自由了
and a warm kiss, I was truly free.
我是不死的 不再只是一個影子
Immortal. No longer just a shadow.
當我抵達紐約的時候
When I arrived in New York,
媒體報道稱我病了
the press reported that I had fallen ill.
SSK字幕組
我讓他們相信了這個傳聞 我知道這些報道
I let them believe it, knowing the reports
SSK字幕組
正是我需要的 它們可以讓娜塔莎飛到我的身邊
were all I would need to have Natacha fly to my side.
當她來到我身邊時
When she came to me,
我與她分享了茂瑙贈予我的黑暗禮物
I shared with her the dark gift Murnau had given to me.
現在我們想與你一起分享它
And now we want to share it with you.
和我們一起走吧
Come away with us.
有一趟明晚出發到紐約的火車
There's a train that leaves tomorrow night to New York.
從那裏可以去歐洲 任何地方
From there, to Europe. Anywhere.
每個地方
Everywhere.
好
Yes.
Yes...
永遠這樣
and forever.
我想你
I missed you.
你聽說了關於舌頭那個謀殺案嗎
You hear the one about the tongue?
兇手用鋸子把受害者的舌頭鋸斷
Cut out of the victim's head with a hacksaw,
然後用錘子把它釘在地板上
then nailed to the floor with a hammer.
她當時還活著呢
While she was alive.
嚇死人了
You're freaking me out.
那個變態就在這兒 就在那扇門後面嗎
That monster is here, right behind that door?
怎麼樣的變態才會想到那種噁心事
What kind of psycho thinks of that shit?
更別說這麼做了
Much less do it.
那他們只讓一個守衛守門嗎
And they only have one guard at the door?
我能搞定任何狀況
I'm plenty enough for anything.
你最好留心那扇門
You better pay attention to that door,
確保沒有任何壞東西跑出來
make sure nothing bad comes out.
嘿 兄弟 你還好吧
Hey, man, you okay?
你是誰
Who are you?
我是雷恩
I'm Wren.
你沒吃你的晚飯
You didn't eat your dinner.
我不想吃那個
I'm not hungry for that.
他們也可以給你弄點別的
They can get you something else.
我不想再吃東西了
I don't want to feed anymore.
他們為什麼把你關在這 雷恩
Why did they put you in here, Wren?
因為我不和他們說話
Because I wouldn't talk to them.
警察嗎
The police officer?
哈恩偵探
Detective Hahn.
他們在電視台找到的你
They found you at the TV station.
你目睹了發生的事情
You saw what happened.
我幫忙了
I helped.
你一定被嚇壞了
You must have been terrified.
你看見的那個人
The man you saw
做了很多壞事
has done a lot of bad things.
醜陋 可怕的事情
Ugly, scary things.
但是你再也不用害怕他了
But you don't have to be afraid of him anymore.
你相信嗎
Do you believe that?
我相信
I do.
但是沒人強迫我做任何事情
But nobody forced me to do anything.
噢 上帝啊
Oh, sweet Jesus.
別動
Don't.
雷恩
Wren.
你殺了保安
You killed the security guard.
他打算抓住他
He was going to catch him.
我希望我們能夠信任彼此 雷恩
I want to know we can trust each other, Wren.
我不會對你撒謊
I won't lie to you.
你能對我做同樣的承諾嗎
Can you promise the same to me?
另外幾次我也在那兒
I was there the other times.
他把那些人的舌頭釘在桌子上的時候
When he nailed their tongues to the table.
他把那對兄弟在床上吊死的時候
When he hung the brothers from the beds.
他切開了他們的肚子
He cut open their stomachs.
那味道真是噁心
It stunk.
你現在相信我嗎
Now do you believe me?
你在那兒
You were there.
但是無論他讓你做什麼
But whatever he made you do,
無論你認為你做了什麼
whatever you think you did...
都是他的責任
he's responsible.
不是你的錯
It's not your fault.
是我的錯
It is my fault.
發生的每件事情
Everything that happened.
拜託
Please,
別這麼說
don't say that.
你聽起來就像我的女兒斯嘉麗
You sound exactly like my daughter Scarlett.
她和你一般大 但她是我知道的最老成的小姑娘了
She's around your age, but she's the oldest little girl I know.
我深信她因為每一件我做的錯事
I think deep down she blames herself
而在心裏責怪她自己
for everything that's wrong with me.
但錯在我
But it's me,
不是她
not her.
同樣的 錯在他
And it's him,
不是你
not you.
我喜歡你
I like you.
你一點都不像我父親
You're nothing like my father.
當我還小的時候
When I was young,
我爸爸告訴我他等不及我長大
my daddy told me he couldn't wait for me to grow up.
他跟我說我會成為他的小淑女
He told me I was gonna be his little lady.
他說話的方式
The way he said it,
讓我的胃都疼起來了
it made my stomach hurt.
令我不想入眠
It got so I didn't want to sleep,
因為我每睜開眼一次 都離長大近了一天
'cause every time I woke up I was a day closer.
有一天他把我留在車裏
One day he left me in a car
自己去科爾特茲喝酒
while he went drinking at the Cortez.
洛杉磯
那天熱瘋了
It was so crazy hot.
車裏就像烤箱一樣
I was like a pizza in the oven.
但我沒有打開窗戶 我什麼都沒說
But I didn't open the window, and I didn't say a word,
因為我想
because I thought
也許有一種我不必長大的方法
maybe there was a way I didn't have to grow up.
但我找到了另一種方法
But I found another way.
現在我想長大可能也沒有那麼糟
Now I think maybe growing up wouldn't have been so bad.
至少不會比現在更糟
It can't be worse than this.
雷恩 我不明白
Wren, I don't understand.
你是在告訴我殺手是你父親嗎
Are you telling me it's your father?
他是殺手
He's the killer?
不 他很早就去世了
No. He died a long time ago.
我只是 我只是煩死這一切了
I'm just... I'm so sick of this whole thing.
我一點都不想再捲入到裏面了
I don't want it anymore.
那麼就放手吧
Then let it go.
-告訴我他是誰 -我不能
- Tell me who he is. - I can't.
為什麼你要保護一個
Why are you protecting someone
根本就不值得你這麼做的人
who doesn't deserve anything from you?
你不會相信我的
You wouldn't believe me.
他會一直殺人
He's going to keep
除非你幫我阻止他
killing people unless you help me stop him.
把我從這兒弄出去 我就告訴你他住在哪兒
Get me out of here, and I'll show you where he lives.
我們現在不是在玩遊戲 雷恩
We're not playing a game here, Wren.
也許該是他被抓的時候了
Maybe it's time he got caught.
我終於開始
I'm finally beginning
感覺到生命回流到我身上了
to feel the life return to me.
我看起來怎樣
How do I look?
糟透了
Terrible.
你就是在誇大其詞
You're being dramatic.
她只比老鼠好那麼一點兒
That was little better than the rats.
我們需要更多
We need more.
噢
Oh.
再多一百倍
A hundred times more.
這種飢渴
This thirst--
是沒法滿足的
it's unslakable.
噢
Oh.
婊子養的
Son of a bitch!
我們被困在這鬼地方多久了
How long have we been trapped in this place?
啊 太久了
Aah. Too long.
我要 把那個男人的頭撕下來
I am going... to rip that man's head off.
我覺得他早就死了
I imagine that he is long dead.
而且老實說 都怪你害我們陷入這樣的困境
And in truth, you are as much to blame for our predicament.
你和你那隻小老鼠
You and your little mouse.
她跟這個無關
She had no part in this.
我們不需要她
We didn't need her.
我們有錢 我們有整個世界
We had money. We had the world.
永恆的生命
Life everlasting.
但你想要你的寵物
But you craved your pet.
她值得嗎
Was she worth it?!
看看我們
Look at us!
「偉大的情聖」
"The Great Lover,"
這張為女人狂熱渴求
that magnificent face that women lusted after,
又陷她們於死境的絕美面孔 現在卻變成奇醜無比的怪物
killed themselves over, reduced to a grotesque monstrosity.
我們的生命被偷走了
Our lives stolen!
一切都沒有了
Everything gone.
你是對的
You are right.
原諒我 親愛的
Forgive me, amore.
我太蠢了
I was foolish.
我保證 我們會重新收回失去的一切
I promise, we will reclaim all that we have lost.
-你在做夢 -你等著看吧
- You are dreaming. - You will see.
我們的生命會比曾經
Our life will be far more glorious
更加輝煌
than it ever was before.
走錯房間了 蠢蛋
Wrong room, asshole!
夥計 那些讀書俱樂部的女士們都趴在我身上
Dude, those book club ladies were all over me.
你看見那個紅頭髮舔我的蛋了嗎
Did you see that redhead lick my balls?
你他媽就是一坨屎
You're so full of shit.
什麼鬼 這兒只有一張床
The hell? There's only one bed.
我才不跟你們這群傻逼分享我的床
I'm not sharing a room with one of you cumsicles.
-啊 -你睡地上
- Ah... - You're sleeping on the floor.
脫衣舞男總是得到最糟糕的房間 哈
Strippers always get the shittiest rooms, huh?
多有趣的生物啊
What curious creatures.
像克羅索斯巨人重返人間
Like the Colossus come to life.
他們血液奔流的聲音簡直震耳欲聾
The gush of their blood is deafening.
我們怎麼會拒絕來自神的禮物呢
Who are we to deny a gift from the gods?
噢
Oh.
威靈頓肯定
Surely the Wellington
在變冷吧 馬奇先生
is getting cold, Mr. March.
幾乎不需擔心 埃弗斯女士
Hardly a concern, Ms. Evers.
或許你的客人要多注意
Perhaps your guest should be mindful
她來訪的時間
of the time she's expected.
我不認為
I don't believe
我在意你的語氣 埃弗斯女士
I care for your tone, Ms. Evers.
這座房子的女主人值得更多的尊重
The lady of the house deserves more respect.
是的 馬奇先生
Yes, Mr. March.
你現在離開一會
You should be elsewhere.
最親愛的
Dearest!
謝謝你今晚和我見面 詹姆斯
Thank you for seeing me tonight, James.
我知道這早了一周
I know it's a week early.
不不 胡說
Mm. Nonsense.
無論什麼時候我都很樂意主辦我們的晚餐
I'd be delighted to host our meal on any night you choose.
我們可以不再一月一次 改成一晚一次
We could have it nightly instead of monthly.
只是說說
Just say the word.
一個月一次 詹姆斯
Once a month, James.
這是我們的安排
That's our arrangement.
我有太多事情要忙了
I'm far too busy for anything more.
當然
Of course.
你要來點阿瑪尼亞克酒嗎
Would you like an Armagnac?
-我要來一杯 -不了 謝謝
- I'm having one. - No, thank you.
說吧
Yes?
我想親自告訴你
I wanted to tell you in person.
我計劃再次結婚
I plan to marry again.
好極了
Splendid!
我當然會替你感到高興了
Why, I couldn't be more pleased.
我們慶祝一下吧 好嗎
Let's have a toast, shall we?
那個幸運的男人是誰
Who's the lucky fellow?
我會送他一些牛排
I'd like to send him some steaks.
威爾·德雷克
Will Drake.
啊 好的
Ah, yes.
那個買下我旅館
That light-in-the-loafers
的同性戀
fellow that bought my hotel.
很好 親愛的 很好
Very good, darling. Very good.
我可以建議你殺他的時候
Might I suggest that when you murder him,
別在旅館裏動手嗎
you do so off the property?
永生的日子裏
It'd be damned awkward
經常撞見他會尷尬死的
to keep running into him for all eternity.
為什麼你認為我會傷害他
And what makes you think I mean to do him harm?
我雖然死了 親愛的 我並不傻
I'm dead, dear. Not stupid.
你怎麼知道我不是找到真愛了呢
And how do you know I haven't found love?
也許是第一次遇上真愛
True love maybe for the very first time.
肯定不是第一次
Surely not for the first time,
馬奇夫人
Mrs. March.
我一直對你恪守誠實 詹姆斯
I've always been scrupulously honest with you, James.
我從來沒有偽裝過我的感受
I never pretended more than I felt.
我也從來沒有聲稱過我愛你
And I never claimed to love you.
是啊
Yes.
哦
Oh.
只是我並不是在說我自己
But then, I wasn't referring to myself now,
是吧
was I?
你什麼意思
What do you mean?
我以為我可以讓你愛我
I thought I could make you love me.
我以為如果我能給你一切
I thought if I gave you everything
你的小心臟所渴望的東西
your little heart desired--
財富 舒適
riches, comfort...
這個旅館
this hotel--
沒有一樣可以感動你
but none of it moved you.
我永遠也無法與那大銀屏上的
I could never compete with the shadow of a god
上帝的影子相匹敵
on a screen, 20 feet tall!
不 讓他走
No, let him go!
-放開她 -放開他
- Let her go! - Let him go!
我懷疑
I have a sneaking suspicion
你可能會錯過你的火車
you're going to miss your train.
哦
Oh.
噢
魯迪
Rudy?
我們在哪
Where are we?
哦天哪
Oh, my God.
是的
Yes.
你的上帝
Your god.
因為我的女王 被困在我所建造的
Trapped within the walls of the palace I built
宮殿的圍牆裏
for my queen.
那就是後面的秘密嗎
That's what was back there?!
不 再是了
Not... anymore.
好了
All right.
走
Go.
好了 我帶你出來了
All right, I got you out.
現在你帶我去見他
Now you take me to him.
雷恩
Wren...
然後我們需要回家
Then we need to go home.
你家在哪
Where?
科爾特茲旅館
The Cortez.
好 別害怕
All right, don't be afraid.
當我找到他 我會把他
When I find him, I'm gonna bury him
深埋 他再也不會重見天日
in a hole so deep, he'll never see the light of day.
是時候讓他停止
It's time to make him stop.
你會殺了他嗎
Will you kill him?
如果我必須要做的話
If I have to.
我真的喜歡你
I really like you.
我不想就這麼結束
I hate to see it end.
再見了 約翰
Good-bye, John.
雷恩
Wren!
不
No!
SSK字幕組